const questions = [
    {
      question: "If I use chemicals at work I must",
      options: ["Be very careful", "Never work alone", "Wear a respirator", "Be specifically trained and authorized"],
      correct: "Be specifically trained and authorized"
    },
    {
      question: "If I have an accident or injury I should",
      options: ["Fix what I broke", "Tell my supervisor", "Keep working and not worry about it", "Report it within a week"],
      correct: "Tell my supervisor"
    },
    {
      question: "Most accidents are caused by",
      options: ["People", "Bad weather", "Equipment", "Poor directions"],
      correct: "People"
    },
    {
      question: "I can help prevent accidents by",
      options: ["Using my own equipment", "Doing only what I am trained to do", "Riding in carpools", "Helping others with their jobs"],
      correct: "Doing only what I am trained to do"
    },
    {
      question: "If I am unsure how to do a job I should",
      options: ["Ask my supervisor", "Try different ways of doing it", "Ask a co-worker", "Do the job slowly"],
      correct: "Ask my supervisor"
    },
    {
      question: "If a very heavy box contains several items, you should",
      options: [
        "Push it across the floor",
        "Carry it on your back",
        "Drag it with a rope or sling",
        "Carry each item separately"
      ],
      correct: "Carry each item separately"
    },
    {
      question: "If you see a lock or tag on an electrical switch",
      options: [
        "You can turn on the switch if it is your equipment",
        "It is ok to use the equipment if no one is working on it",
        "You must not touch the switch",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      correct: "You must not touch the switch"
    },
    {
      question: "Machine guards are",
      options: [
        "People who guard equipment",
        "Plates and covers that go over hazardous equipment parts",
        "Not required at your workplace",
        "Can be moved or removed by any employee"
      ],
      correct: "Plates and covers that go over hazardous equipment parts"
    },
    {
      question: "One of the hazards of confined spaces is",
      options: [
        "Entrapment",
        "Color blindness",
        "Hand cramps",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      correct: "Entrapment"
    },
    {
      question: "Voltage at or above which value is considered hazardous?",
      options: [
        " 10 Volts",
        "30 Volts",
        "110 Volts",
        "240 Volts"
      ],
      correct: "110 Volts"
    },
  ];
  
  export default questions;
  